{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133853031","data":{"timestamp":" 947133853031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133857082","data":{"timestamp":" 947133857082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133874201","data":{"timestamp":" 947133874201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133879554","data":{"timestamp":" 947133879554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133888299","data":{"timestamp":" 947133888299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133894285","data":{"timestamp":" 947133894284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133898656","data":{"timestamp":" 947133898656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133904504","data":{"timestamp":" 947133904504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133909799","data":{"timestamp":" 947133909799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133923000","data":{"timestamp":" 947133922999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133926781","data":{"timestamp":" 947133926780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133932214","data":{"timestamp":" 947133932214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133936600","data":{"timestamp":" 947133936599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133941667","data":{"timestamp":" 947133941667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133945781","data":{"timestamp":" 947133945781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133957039","data":{"timestamp":" 947133957039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133962336","data":{"timestamp":" 947133962335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133965759","data":{"timestamp":" 947133965759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133971337","data":{"timestamp":" 947133971337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133976881","data":{"timestamp":" 947133976881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133980780","data":{"timestamp":" 947133980780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133984655","data":{"timestamp":" 947133984655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133988037","data":{"timestamp":" 947133988037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133991630","data":{"timestamp":" 947133991630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133995922","data":{"timestamp":" 947133995922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133999518","data":{"timestamp":" 947133999518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134004055","data":{"timestamp":" 947134004055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_B-R-T"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134009880","data":{"timestamp":" 947134009880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134015654","data":{"timestamp":" 947134015653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 69c2f264-dc2d-4d9c-8042-5303b41ee086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134030515","data":{"timestamp":" 947134030514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134032645","data":{"timestamp":" 947134032645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134034781","data":{"timestamp":" 947134034780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134038035","data":{"timestamp":" 947134038034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134040310","data":{"timestamp":" 947134040309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134042556","data":{"timestamp":" 947134042555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134045473","data":{"timestamp":" 947134045473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134047708","data":{"timestamp":" 947134047707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134049925","data":{"timestamp":" 947134049924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134053195","data":{"timestamp":" 947134053195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134055269","data":{"timestamp":" 947134055268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134057419","data":{"timestamp":" 947134057417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134060451","data":{"timestamp":" 947134060450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134062686","data":{"timestamp":" 947134062686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134064944","data":{"timestamp":" 947134064943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134067983","data":{"timestamp":" 947134067982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134070387","data":{"timestamp":" 947134070386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134072721","data":{"timestamp":" 947134072720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134075811","data":{"timestamp":" 947134075811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134077948","data":{"timestamp":" 947134077947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134080095","data":{"timestamp":" 947134080095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134083271","data":{"timestamp":" 947134083270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134085452","data":{"timestamp":" 947134085451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134087645","data":{"timestamp":" 947134087644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134090808","data":{"timestamp":" 947134090807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134093236","data":{"timestamp":" 947134093236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134095659","data":{"timestamp":" 947134095658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134098842","data":{"timestamp":" 947134098842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134101094","data":{"timestamp":" 947134101093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134103394","data":{"timestamp":" 947134103393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134106383","data":{"timestamp":" 947134106381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134108630","data":{"timestamp":" 947134108629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134110877","data":{"timestamp":" 947134110877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134113892","data":{"timestamp":" 947134113891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134116254","data":{"timestamp":" 947134116253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134118645","data":{"timestamp":" 947134118644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134121827","data":{"timestamp":" 947134121827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134124210","data":{"timestamp":" 947134124209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134126624","data":{"timestamp":" 947134126623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134129639","data":{"timestamp":" 947134129639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134131952","data":{"timestamp":" 947134131951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134134261","data":{"timestamp":" 947134134260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134137519","data":{"timestamp":" 947134137518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134139810","data":{"timestamp":" 947134139810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134142099","data":{"timestamp":" 947134142098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134145502","data":{"timestamp":" 947134145501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134147916","data":{"timestamp":" 947134147915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134150383","data":{"timestamp":" 947134150383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134153288","data":{"timestamp":" 947134153287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134155493","data":{"timestamp":" 947134155492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134157703","data":{"timestamp":" 947134157702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134161138","data":{"timestamp":" 947134161137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134163473","data":{"timestamp":" 947134163472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134165808","data":{"timestamp":" 947134165807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134168948","data":{"timestamp":" 947134168947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134171238","data":{"timestamp":" 947134171237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134173525","data":{"timestamp":" 947134173524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134176556","data":{"timestamp":" 947134176555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134178670","data":{"timestamp":" 947134178669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134180835","data":{"timestamp":" 947134180835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134183996","data":{"timestamp":" 947134183995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134186268","data":{"timestamp":" 947134186267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134188566","data":{"timestamp":" 947134188565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134191838","data":{"timestamp":" 947134191837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134194064","data":{"timestamp":" 947134194064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134196304","data":{"timestamp":" 947134196303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134199575","data":{"timestamp":" 947134199574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134201923","data":{"timestamp":" 947134201923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134204241","data":{"timestamp":" 947134204241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134207422","data":{"timestamp":" 947134207421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134209730","data":{"timestamp":" 947134209729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134212074","data":{"timestamp":" 947134212073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134215489","data":{"timestamp":" 947134215488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134215583","data":{"timestamp":" 947134215583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 080e0c31-03a9-49ce-9fa3-e647a4513146"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134231578","data":{"timestamp":" 947134231577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134231960","data":{"timestamp":" 947134231959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134232453","data":{"timestamp":" 947134232452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134232807","data":{"timestamp":" 947134232807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134233221","data":{"timestamp":" 947134233221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134233709","data":{"timestamp":" 947134233708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134233944","data":{"timestamp":" 947134233944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134237162","data":{"timestamp":" 947134237161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134237202","data":{"timestamp":" 947134237202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134237931","data":{"timestamp":" 947134237930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134238338","data":{"timestamp":" 947134238337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134238646","data":{"timestamp":" 947134238646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134238864","data":{"timestamp":" 947134238863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134239073","data":{"timestamp":" 947134239072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134239403","data":{"timestamp":" 947134239402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134239639","data":{"timestamp":" 947134239639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134242784","data":{"timestamp":" 947134242783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134243196","data":{"timestamp":" 947134243196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134245790","data":{"timestamp":" 947134245789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134246004","data":{"timestamp":" 947134246002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134246219","data":{"timestamp":" 947134246218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134249698","data":{"timestamp":" 947134249698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134253509","data":{"timestamp":" 947134253507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134254548","data":{"timestamp":" 947134254546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134257292","data":{"timestamp":" 947134257291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134257678","data":{"timestamp":" 947134257677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134258171","data":{"timestamp":" 947134258170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134258528","data":{"timestamp":" 947134258528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134258947","data":{"timestamp":" 947134258946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134259435","data":{"timestamp":" 947134259434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134259669","data":{"timestamp":" 947134259669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134262906","data":{"timestamp":" 947134262905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134262942","data":{"timestamp":" 947134262942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134263670","data":{"timestamp":" 947134263669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134264076","data":{"timestamp":" 947134264075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134264382","data":{"timestamp":" 947134264381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134264598","data":{"timestamp":" 947134264597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134264806","data":{"timestamp":" 947134264806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134265135","data":{"timestamp":" 947134265134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134265370","data":{"timestamp":" 947134265370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134267961","data":{"timestamp":" 947134267959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134268068","data":{"timestamp":" 947134268068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 368a751b-5b35-4b55-9679-1ec21e493347"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134296059","data":{"timestamp":" 947134296059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134307200","data":{"timestamp":" 947134307199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134308788","data":{"timestamp":" 947134308787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134313457","data":{"timestamp":" 947134313457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134315089","data":{"timestamp":" 947134315088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134318561","data":{"timestamp":" 947134318560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134320171","data":{"timestamp":" 947134320170"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134323676","data":{"timestamp":" 947134323676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134325309","data":{"timestamp":" 947134325308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134328734","data":{"timestamp":" 947134328734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134330366","data":{"timestamp":" 947134330365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134335624","data":{"timestamp":" 947134335624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134337254","data":{"timestamp":" 947134337253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134340668","data":{"timestamp":" 947134340667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" START_ANASOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134343880","data":{"timestamp":" 947134343880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134345501","data":{"timestamp":" 947134345500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134348492","data":{"timestamp":" 947134348492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134350090","data":{"timestamp":" 947134350088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134353091","data":{"timestamp":" 947134353087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134354699","data":{"timestamp":" 947134354698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134357949","data":{"timestamp":" 947134357948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134359576","data":{"timestamp":" 947134359576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134362539","data":{"timestamp":" 947134362539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134364560","data":{"timestamp":" 947134364559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134364700","data":{"timestamp":" 947134364700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" cacdaf64-fa08-49ef-b0e4-83ad371b48f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134386067","data":{"timestamp":" 947134386067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134391495","data":{"timestamp":" 947134391494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134393102","data":{"timestamp":" 947134393101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134395949","data":{"timestamp":" 947134395948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134397581","data":{"timestamp":" 947134397580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134401561","data":{"timestamp":" 947134401561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134403165","data":{"timestamp":" 947134403164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134406882","data":{"timestamp":" 947134406882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" START_ANAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134418066","data":{"timestamp":" 947134418066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134419726","data":{"timestamp":" 947134419725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134422547","data":{"timestamp":" 947134422547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" START_ALICHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134425719","data":{"timestamp":" 947134425719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134427289","data":{"timestamp":" 947134427289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134431819","data":{"timestamp":" 947134431818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134433432","data":{"timestamp":" 947134433431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134436467","data":{"timestamp":" 947134436467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134438093","data":{"timestamp":" 947134438092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134441909","data":{"timestamp":" 947134441908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" START_AKALALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134445848","data":{"timestamp":" 947134445848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134447472","data":{"timestamp":" 947134447472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134450485","data":{"timestamp":" 947134450484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134452098","data":{"timestamp":" 947134452097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134455578","data":{"timestamp":" 947134455577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134457175","data":{"timestamp":" 947134457174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134459910","data":{"timestamp":" 947134459910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134461931","data":{"timestamp":" 947134461929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134462050","data":{"timestamp":" 947134462050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" b9f20a81-d6c8-4253-b4e7-8902932427b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134487921","data":{"timestamp":" 947134487921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_l-a-b"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134491815","data":{"timestamp":" 947134491815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134495520","data":{"timestamp":" 947134495520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_r-o-a"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134499515","data":{"timestamp":" 947134499515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-z-w"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134503162","data":{"timestamp":" 947134503162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_g-a-t"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134509390","data":{"timestamp":" 947134509390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_u-a-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134513879","data":{"timestamp":" 947134513879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-s-l"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134522314","data":{"timestamp":" 947134522314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-k-a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134529753","data":{"timestamp":" 947134529752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_z-a-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134535171","data":{"timestamp":" 947134535171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-h-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134540957","data":{"timestamp":" 947134540955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 51afd752-78b5-45bf-be1e-1c52bd565b2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-h-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134566219","data":{"timestamp":" 947134566219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134572875","data":{"timestamp":" 947134572875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_j"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134579513","data":{"timestamp":" 947134579512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_a_n"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134586152","data":{"timestamp":" 947134586151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_a_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134592807","data":{"timestamp":" 947134592805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_a_u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134599494","data":{"timestamp":" 947134599493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134606130","data":{"timestamp":" 947134606129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_u_a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134612802","data":{"timestamp":" 947134612802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_b_a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134619460","data":{"timestamp":" 947134619460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_y_a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134626099","data":{"timestamp":" 947134626098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_r_a_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..A.all.10.rand.say.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134638162","data":{"timestamp":" 947134638162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 6f098591-2bd7-47bf-94e3-df8d88fb24de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_r_a_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134668305","data":{"timestamp":" 947134668305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134671125","data":{"timestamp":" 947134671125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134672750","data":{"timestamp":" 947134672749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134676409","data":{"timestamp":" 947134676409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134678014","data":{"timestamp":" 947134678013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134680534","data":{"timestamp":" 947134680534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134682134","data":{"timestamp":" 947134682133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134684566","data":{"timestamp":" 947134684566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134686180","data":{"timestamp":" 947134686179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134688491","data":{"timestamp":" 947134688491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134690087","data":{"timestamp":" 947134690086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134693917","data":{"timestamp":" 947134693917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134695515","data":{"timestamp":" 947134695514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134701975","data":{"timestamp":" 947134701974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134703586","data":{"timestamp":" 947134703586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134715231","data":{"timestamp":" 947134715230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134716849","data":{"timestamp":" 947134716848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134719510","data":{"timestamp":" 947134719509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134721123","data":{"timestamp":" 947134721122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134725646","data":{"timestamp":" 947134725646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134727265","data":{"timestamp":" 947134727264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134729588","data":{"timestamp":" 947134729587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134731200","data":{"timestamp":" 947134731199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134733839","data":{"timestamp":" 947134733839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134735438","data":{"timestamp":" 947134735437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134738221","data":{"timestamp":" 947134738220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134739852","data":{"timestamp":" 947134739851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134742440","data":{"timestamp":" 947134742439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134744067","data":{"timestamp":" 947134744067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134746469","data":{"timestamp":" 947134746469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134748063","data":{"timestamp":" 947134748062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134750736","data":{"timestamp":" 947134750734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134752369","data":{"timestamp":" 947134752368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134754863","data":{"timestamp":" 947134754863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134756470","data":{"timestamp":" 947134756469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134758935","data":{"timestamp":" 947134758935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134760535","data":{"timestamp":" 947134760534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134762795","data":{"timestamp":" 947134762794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134764402","data":{"timestamp":" 947134764401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134767123","data":{"timestamp":" 947134767122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134768725","data":{"timestamp":" 947134768725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134771298","data":{"timestamp":" 947134771297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134772906","data":{"timestamp":" 947134772906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134775397","data":{"timestamp":" 947134775397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134777007","data":{"timestamp":" 947134777006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134779373","data":{"timestamp":" 947134779373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134780965","data":{"timestamp":" 947134780964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134783585","data":{"timestamp":" 947134783584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134785615","data":{"timestamp":" 947134785614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134785706","data":{"timestamp":" 947134785706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134856081","data":{"timestamp":" 947134856080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" c3304423-995c-4fe5-8ac1-ff9fd4ca47bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947134873046","data":{"timestamp":" 947134873046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_074353"," gameId":" 903efce3-fba1-4123-bfe3-da59a5e9abc2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}